{
  "inputTimeWaitSecs": 	240,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "-98 &times; 6",
      "answer": "-588"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2375 &#xF7; -16",
      "answer": "148 7/16",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-8538 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "-1707 3/5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-92 &times; -10",
      "answer": "920"
    },
    {
      "question": "-7846 &#xF7; -14",
      "answer": "560 3/7",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "(-97)&sup2;",
      "answer": "9409"
    },
    {
      "question": "82 &times; 259",
      "answer": "21238"
    },
    {
      "question": "(349)&sup2;",
      "answer": "121801"
    },
    {
      "question": "3790 &#xF7; -3",
      "answer": "-1263 1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "127 &times; -43",
      "answer": "-5461"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4566 &#xF7; -3",
      "answer": "1522",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-8097 &#xF7; -10",
      "answer": "809 7/10",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "499 &times; 66",
      "answer": "32934"
    },
    {
      "question": "169 &times; -66",
      "answer": "-11154"
    },
    {
      "question": "-161 &times; -47",
      "answer": "7567"
    },
    {
      "question": "285 &times; 2",
      "answer": "570"
    },
    {
      "question": "149 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "49 2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "91 &times; -17",
      "answer": "-1547"
    },
    {
      "question": "-28 &times; -56",
      "answer": "1568"
    },
    {
      "question": "145 &times; -25",
      "answer": "-3625"
    },
    {
      "question": "-41 &times; 499",
      "answer": "-20459"
    },
    {
      "question": "-127 &times; 51",
      "answer": "-6477"
    },
    {
      "question": "(-14)&sup3;",
      "answer": "-2744"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2649 &#xF7; -4",
      "answer": "662 1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-433 &#xF7; 9",
      "answer": "-48 1/9",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "6518 &#xF7; 4",
      "answer": "1629 1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-62 &times; 106",
      "answer": "-6572"
    },
    {
      "question": "9086 &#xF7; 15",
      "answer": "605 11/15",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-402 &times; 16",
      "answer": "-6432"
    },
    {
      "question": "9114 &#xF7; -7",
      "answer": "-1302",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-7309 &#xF7; -4",
      "answer": "1827 1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "8259 &#xF7; -8",
      "answer": "-1032 3/8",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "3243 &#xF7; -12",
      "answer": "-270 1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "18 &times; 384",
      "answer": "6912"
    },
    {
      "question": "(-17)&sup3;",
      "answer": "-4913"
    },
    {
      "question": "345 &times; 57",
      "answer": "19665"
    },
    {
      "question": "(345)&sup2;",
      "answer": "119025"
    },
    {
      "question": "79 &times; 105",
      "answer": "8295"
    },
    {
      "question": "-272 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "-34",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "1127 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "93 11/12",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-55 &times; -56",
      "answer": "3080"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4810 &#xF7; 15",
      "answer": "-320 2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "7995 &#xF7; -2",
      "answer": "-3997 1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-96 &times; 74",
      "answer": "-7104"
    },
    {
      "question": "100 &times; -310",
      "answer": "-31000"
    },
    {
      "question": "830 &#xF7; -2",
      "answer": "-415",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "342 &times; 23",
      "answer": "7866"
    },
    {
      "question": "-308 &times; 42",
      "answer": "-12936"
    },
    {
      "question": "-7166 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "-1023 5/7",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "3390 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "484 2/7",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "399 &times; 80",
      "answer": "31920"
    },
    {
      "question": "44 &times; -65",
      "answer": "-2860"
    },
    {
      "question": "-17 &times; -231",
      "answer": "3927"
    },
    {
      "question": "373 &#xF7; -6",
      "answer": "-62 1/6",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-3404 &#xF7; -15",
      "answer": "226 14/15",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "565 &#xF7; -3",
      "answer": "-188 1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-320 &times; -34",
      "answer": "10880"
    },
    {
      "question": "(15)&sup3;",
      "answer": "3375"
    },
    {
      "question": "41 &times; 90",
      "answer": "3690"
    },
    {
      "question": "(71)&sup2;",
      "answer": "5041"
    },
    {
      "question": "2860 &#xF7; 15",
      "answer": "190 2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "3199 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "1066 1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "42 &times; -460",
      "answer": "-19320"
    },
    {
      "question": "-9 &times; 468",
      "answer": "-4212"
    },
    {
      "question": "-555 &#xF7; 15",
      "answer": "-37",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "220 &times; -40",
      "answer": "-8800"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4899 &#xF7; -8",
      "answer": "612 3/8",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "3124 &#xF7; -3",
      "answer": "-1041 1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "121 &times; 42",
      "answer": "5082"
    },
    {
      "question": "4981 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "711 4/7",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "1706 &#xF7; 16",
      "answer": "106 5/8",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-3386 &#xF7; -9",
      "answer": "376 2/9",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-9787 &#xF7; 13",
      "answer": "-752 11/13",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "37 &times; 413",
      "answer": "15281"
    },
    {
      "question": "9205 &#xF7; -13",
      "answer": "-708 1/13",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-9151 &#xF7; -16",
      "answer": "571 15/16",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "5059 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "1011 4/5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-337 &times; 17",
      "answer": "-5729"
    },
    {
      "question": "-240 &times; 6",
      "answer": "-1440"
    },
    {
      "question": "-272 &times; 23",
      "answer": "-6256"
    },
    {
      "question": "45 &times; 212",
      "answer": "9540"
    },
    {
      "question": "3012 &#xF7; -8",
      "answer": "-376 1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &times; 38",
      "answer": "380"
    },
    {
      "question": "-8 &times; -225",
      "answer": "1800"
    },
    {
      "question": "-9883 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "-3294 1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "1644 &#xF7; -2",
      "answer": "-822",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-3215 &#xF7; -16",
      "answer": "200 15/16",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "3837 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "383 7/10",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "3462 &#xF7; -13",
      "answer": "-266 4/13",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "7701 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "770 1/10",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-1360 &#xF7; -4",
      "answer": "340",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-2285 &#xF7; -11",
      "answer": "207 8/11",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "(12)&sup3;",
      "answer": "1728"
    },
    {
      "question": "5737 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "1912 1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "8835 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "2945",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "13 &times; -41",
      "answer": "-533"
    },
    {
      "question": "5352 &#xF7; -6",
      "answer": "-892",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-8053 &#xF7; 11",
      "answer": "-732 1/11",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-4407 &#xF7; -9",
      "answer": "489 2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "5196 &#xF7; -16",
      "answer": "-324 3/4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "(21)&sup3;",
      "answer": "9261"
    },
    {
      "question": "92 &times; -2",
      "answer": "-184"
    },
    {
      "question": "8573 &#xF7; -13",
      "answer": "-659 6/13",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-21 &times; -131",
      "answer": "2751"
    },
    {
      "question": "7503 &#xF7; -14",
      "answer": "-535 13/14",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-6306 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "-1261 1/5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "4491 &#xF7; -2",
      "answer": "-2245 1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-85 &times; 27",
      "answer": "-2295"
    },
    {
      "question": "-20 &times; -201",
      "answer": "4020"
    },
    {
      "question": "-7 &times; -308",
      "answer": "2156"
    },
    {
      "question": "-6997 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "-583 1/12",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "23 &times; -58",
      "answer": "-1334"
    },
    {
      "question": "-377 &times; -81",
      "answer": "30537"
    },
    {
      "question": "-90 &times; -365",
      "answer": "32850"
    },
    {
      "question": "-5508 &#xF7; -9",
      "answer": "612",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-1162 &#xF7; -11",
      "answer": "105 7/11",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "(240)&sup2;",
      "answer": "57600"
    },
    {
      "question": "-64 &times; 465",
      "answer": "-29760"
    },
    {
      "question": "(-22)&sup3;",
      "answer": "-10648"
    },
    {
      "question": "6280 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "1256",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-219 &times; 62",
      "answer": "-13578"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2842 &#xF7; -16",
      "answer": "177 5/8",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-83 &times; -97",
      "answer": "8051"
    },
    {
      "question": "-67 &times; -435",
      "answer": "29145"
    },
    {
      "question": "-14 &times; -392",
      "answer": "5488"
    },
    {
      "question": "(-40)&sup3;",
      "answer": "-64000"
    },
    {
      "question": "6774 &#xF7; -5",
      "answer": "-1354 4/5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "27 &times; 89",
      "answer": "2403"
    },
    {
      "question": "(-35)&sup2;",
      "answer": "1225"
    },
    {
      "question": "-3769 &#xF7; 14",
      "answer": "-269 3/14",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "5299 &#xF7; -13",
      "answer": "-407 8/13",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "2649 &#xF7; -12",
      "answer": "-220 3/4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "1281 &#xF7; 9",
      "answer": "142 1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-1339 &#xF7; -5",
      "answer": "267 4/5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "456 &times; -16",
      "answer": "-7296"
    },
    {
      "question": "7274 &#xF7; -9",
      "answer": "-808 2/9",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-361 &times; -12",
      "answer": "4332"
    },
    {
      "question": "(-11)&sup3;",
      "answer": "-1331"
    },
    {
      "question": "961 &#xF7; 13",
      "answer": "73 12/13",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "53 &times; 3",
      "answer": "159"
    },
    {
      "question": "-179 &times; 0",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "-9287 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "-1326 5/7",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-51 &times; -90",
      "answer": "4590"
    },
    {
      "question": "-427 &times; -2",
      "answer": "854"
    },
    {
      "question": "28 &times; -230",
      "answer": "-6440"
    },
    {
      "question": "-58 &times; -48",
      "answer": "2784"
    },
    {
      "question": "-1001 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "-200 1/5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "107 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "35 2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "3720 &#xF7; 14",
      "answer": "265 5/7",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "(488)&sup2;",
      "answer": "238144"
    },
    {
      "question": "425 &#xF7; -3",
      "answer": "-141 2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-26 &times; 108",
      "answer": "-2808"
    },
    {
      "question": "(155)&sup2;",
      "answer": "24025"
    },
    {
      "question": "9182 &#xF7; -2",
      "answer": "-4591",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-6212 &#xF7; -14",
      "answer": "443 5/7",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-3515 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "-351 1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-8503 &#xF7; -7",
      "answer": "1214 5/7",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "142 &times; -4",
      "answer": "-568"
    },
    {
      "question": "51 &times; -226",
      "answer": "-11526"
    },
    {
      "question": "(374)&sup2;",
      "answer": "139876"
    },
    {
      "question": "(302)&sup2;",
      "answer": "91204"
    },
    {
      "question": "-1031 &#xF7; 4",
      "answer": "-257 3/4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "48 &times; 36",
      "answer": "1728"
    },
    {
      "question": "-3790 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "-473 3/4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-9816 &#xF7; 4",
      "answer": "-2454",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "1801 &#xF7; -4",
      "answer": "-450 1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "8984 &#xF7; -15",
      "answer": "-598 14/15",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-104 &times; 83",
      "answer": "-8632"
    },
    {
      "question": "31 &times; -114",
      "answer": "-3534"
    },
    {
      "question": "5106 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "638 1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-2606 &#xF7; 9",
      "answer": "-289 5/9",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-2094 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "-698",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "(-64)&sup2;",
      "answer": "4096"
    },
    {
      "question": "(-169)&sup2;",
      "answer": "28561"
    },
    {
      "question": "58 &times; -415",
      "answer": "-24070"
    },
    {
      "question": "-3863 &#xF7; 15",
      "answer": "-257 8/15",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "5849 &#xF7; -14",
      "answer": "-417 11/14",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "20 &times; -396",
      "answer": "-7920"
    },
    {
      "question": "-1713 &#xF7; -15",
      "answer": "114 1/5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "(-102)&sup2;",
      "answer": "10404"
    },
    {
      "question": "4950 &#xF7; -12",
      "answer": "-412 1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "(219)&sup2;",
      "answer": "47961"
    },
    {
      "question": "2173 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "362 1/6",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-9429 &#xF7; 4",
      "answer": "-2357 1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-189 &times; 28",
      "answer": "-5292"
    },
    {
      "question": "7957 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "795 7/10",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-7269 &#xF7; 13",
      "answer": "-559 2/13",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "(-229)&sup2;",
      "answer": "52441"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &times; -342",
      "answer": "-4104"
    },
    {
      "question": "-8264 &#xF7; -10",
      "answer": "826 2/5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "300 &times; 8",
      "answer": "2400"
    },
    {
      "question": "240 &times; 44",
      "answer": "10560"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2900 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "-414 2/7",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "2713 &#xF7; -14",
      "answer": "-193 11/14",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &times; 263",
      "answer": "2367"
    },
    {
      "question": "-146 &times; -64",
      "answer": "9344"
    },
    {
      "question": "427 &times; 79",
      "answer": "33733"
    },
    {
      "question": "-7648 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "-764 4/5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-8332 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "-1666 2/5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-7375 &#xF7; -10",
      "answer": "737 1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
